HorrorLight.
HorrorLight is a 3D horror game in which you play a character locked in a labyrinth.
It is at the first person view.
You can walk for the discretion …
Or you can run for your life,
Until you find the exit …
Or until you die!
There are 3 modes: Escape, Survivor and Infection.
The humans are looking for an exit,
Whereas the monsters are looking for the humans.
All modes are playable in multiplayer and it’s highly recommended to play with friends.
You can use as a human or as a monster a lot of bonuses!
Rayon X vision, invisibility, minimap …
And you can place a lot of trap:
Blind mine, fake exit, immobilize mine…
Be the hunter or the hunted!
Choose your side!
Available in October 2017.