HorrorLight.
HorrorLight is a 3D horror game in which you play a character locked in a labyrinth.
It is at the first person view.
You can walk for the discretion …
Or you can run for your life,
Until you find the exit …
Or until you die!
There are 3 modes: Escape, Survivor and Infection.
In escape mode, there are humans and monsters at the beginning.
In a given time, the humans are looking for an exit,
Whereas the monsters are looking for the humans.
Be careful, don’t team up with humans!
When a human go through an exit, this exit disappears and another is randomly placed.
And it can kill you! Or just makes you lose.
In survivor mode, there are humans at the beginning and monsters are appearing over time.
The humans must survive the longest possible and find the most exits before dying.
Likewise, don’t team up with humans!
They will steal you exits and your score will stay low until you die!
In infection mode, there are more humans than monsters at the beginning.
In a given time, the monsters must infect the most humans possible before they reach the exit.
You can team up with humans: the more humans escaped, the less humans infected.
But be careful, if they are infected you can quickly be infected too.
All modes are playable in multiplayer and it’s highly recommended to play with friends.
You can use as a human or as a monster a lot of bonuses!
Rayon X vision, invisibility, minimap …
And you can place a lot of trap:
Blind mine, fake exit, immobilize mine…
Be the hunter or the hunted!
Choose your side!
Available in October 2017.